So, what you're eating
is not technically yogurt.
(Leonard:)It doesn't have enough
live acidophilus cultures.
It's really just ice milk
with carrageenan added for thickness.
- Well, that's very interesting.
- It's also not pink and has no berries.
(Penny:)Yeah, but it doesn't really
answer my question.
- What was your question again?
- Do you want some?
(Penny:)Ah.
(Leonard:)- Right. No. I'm lactose intolerant.
- Right.
- So gas.
- Yeah, got it.
(Leonard:)Well, good night.
- What are you doing?
- There was a draft.
PENNY:
I didn't feel a draft.
- Why don't we just go into your...?
- Oh, yeah.
(Penny:)Maybe we should
slow things down a little.
(Leonard:)No, I didn't mean
to go into your apartment to go fast.